

# **Nguyen Duc Vu**

PHP Developer

vunguyenbn97@gmail.com

0977 468 402

• Ha Noi

https://linkedin.com/in/vund-dev

https://github.com/vund-dev

## **CAREER OBJECTIVES**

I have more than 4 years of software development experience in Product and OutSource projects.

Currently, I am working at TopCV Vietnam Joint Stock Company with products for candidates and employers.

OutSource projects develop image processing applications, vehicle recognition, IoT applications, and e-commerce for the Japanese market. My upcoming goal is to work at professional technology companies. I want to learn more from experienced colleagues, contribute to the company as well as develop myself to become a Senior Developer or Technical Leader.

## WORK EXPERIENCES

TopCV VietNam JSC

06/2021 - Now

Junior Developer, Middle Developer

Develop and maintain products for candidates, employers, and internal operations system using technologies such as PHP Laravel, ReactJS, VueJS, NodeJS, MySQL, MongoDB, Elasticsearch, Kafka, Design Patterns (Dependency Injection, Repository, Facade, Singleton), and more.

Vistarsoft Global Co., Ltd

10/2019 - 06/2021

Fresher Developer, Junior Developer

Develop and maintain applications support Japanese traffic using C++, OpenCV, Python, image processing, IoT

### **EDUCATION**

Ha Noi University of Industry

2015 - 2019

Information Technology

## **SKILLS**

Technologies

C++, Python, PHP, Laravel, MySQL, MongoDB, Kafka Streams, Elasticsearch, Microservices, DomainDriven Design (DDD), Redis, Design Patterns (Dependency Injection, Repository, Facade, Singleton), NestJS, ReactJS, VueJS, HTML, CSS, JS,TS, Jquery, Git, Linux, MacOS

Languages Basic English reading and writing

## **PROJECTS**

#### Tuyendung.topcv.vn (03/2023 - now)

Company	TopCV VietNam JSC
Description	Smart recruitment platform for employers, supporting finding suitable candidates. Apply Al technology to products. Main features such as: Recruitment campaign, Post job ads, Find CV, Recommend CV, Manage CV, Provide paid service packages for employers,
Team Size	Agile Team 11
Positions	Middle Developer
Responsibilities	<ul> <li>Participate in developing features such as Posting job advertisements, Searching CVs, Recommend CV, Managing CVs, including interfaces, APIs, Databases.</li> <li>Optimize queries, refactor code</li> <li>Resolve bugs that arise in the production environment</li> <li>Join the Agile team in evaluating and contributing ideas to build new features.</li> </ul>
Technologies	Laravel, VueJS, SCSS, React Native, MySQL, MongoDB, Elasticsearch, Kafka, Design Patterns (Dependency Injection, Repository, Facade, Singleton), Microservices Architecture, Domain-Driven Design

# Internal Operation System (09/2021 - 03/2023)

Company	TopCV VietNam JSC
Description	Products operated internally by the Company. Has main features such as: Workflow, Customer Tracking, Human Resource Management, CRM,
Team Size	Agile Team 10
Positions	- Junior Developer (09/2021 - 04/2022) - Middle Developer (04/2022 - 03/2023)
Responsibilities	<ul> <li>Participate in building and developing professional features to support sales and customer care staff.</li> <li>Participate in building process systems and managing Workflow processes.</li> <li>Participate in building Microservices about: Accounts, Customers, Human Resources, Workflow,</li> <li>Participate in building and designing Database for features in the project.</li> <li>Optimize the experience in the system.</li> <li>Join the Agile team in evaluating and contributing ideas to build new features.</li> </ul>
Technologies	Laravel, NestJS, ReactJS, Microservices Architecture, Domain-Driven Design (DDD), Kafka, Design Patterns (Dependency Injection, Repository, Facade, Singleton), Elasticsearch, MySQL, MongoDB

# **Topcv.vn** (06/2021 - 09/2021)

Company	TopCV VietNam JSC
Description	One of the Company's core products with services such as supporting free online CV creation tools, finding jobs for candidates and some other features.
Team Size	5
Positions	Junior Developer
Responsibilities	<ul> <li>Participate in developing cv templates</li> <li>Develop candidate vip feature</li> <li>Optimize and increase candidate experience</li> </ul>
Technologies	Laravel, MySQL, Elasticsearch, HTML, CSS, JQuery,

# **Wedding E-commerce** (02/2020 - 06/2021)

Customer	Japan
Description	Online weddings are becoming more and more popular, celebrating wedding guests is easier with online shopping services according to the couple's wishes.
Team Size	5
Positions	Junior Developer
Responsibilities	<ul> <li>Participate in building and designing Database for features in the project</li> <li>Develop backend and frontend product modules</li> </ul>
Technologies	Laravel, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Jquery

# **Traffic Guide Application** (10/2019 - 06/2021)

Customer	Japan
Description	Solve the problem of traffic guide at road maintenance construction sites
Team Size	5
Positions	- Fresher Developer (10/2019 - 01/2020) - Junior Developer (01/2020 - 06/2021)
Responsibilities	<ul> <li>Develop lane recognition service</li> <li>Training model, improving the accuracy of identifying vehicles and license plates</li> <li>Fix errors that occur during actual runtime and optimize performance</li> <li>Develop web service to support remote object location</li> <li>Coordinate with BrSE in Japan when installing experimental products at off-road construction sites</li> </ul>
Technologies	C++, Python, OpenCV, Yolo, Laravel, HTML, CSS, JQuery